export const Data = [
    {Prompt:"2+3", Options:[3, 4, 5, 6], Answer:3},
    {Prompt:"7*8", Options:[41, 65, 42, 56], Answer:4},
    {Prompt:"31-9", Options:[23, 22, 20, 29], Answer:2},
    {Prompt:"17*2", Options:[34, 24, 27, 37], Answer:1},
    {Prompt:"78*2", Options:[140, 146, 156, 158], Answer:3},
    {Prompt:"1000-279", Options:[821, 721, 729, 630], Answer:2},
    {Prompt:"108/12", Options:[9, 11, 8, 7], Answer:1},
    {Prompt:"33*33", Options:[9999, 1999, 1099, 1089], Answer:4},
    {Prompt:"-74+140", Options:[66, -66, 214, 198], Answer:1},
    {Prompt:"1331/11", Options:[121, 131, 133, 122], Answer:1},
]